

Rushikesh Ghule

- 9665961721
- rushikeshghule26@gmail.com
- Pune Maharashtra, India.

Personal Profile

Professional validation engineer with 1 month of experience in pharmaceutical, and 2 years experience in medical field as a pharmacist, and Social media executive with 1 year experience in Instagram Ads.

Skills

- > Html, Css
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- WordPress
- Knowledge of Drugs
- Excel , word
- Instagram Ads
- Front-End Development

Accomplishments

- Certificate in WordPress by Vision Academy
- Certificate in Digital Marketing by Google Digital Unlocked.

Education

Pune University	
BBA(CA)	2019 - 2022
Class XII with First Class	2018 - 2019
S M Joshi Vidyalaya	
Class X With Second Class	2016 - 2017

Courses

Fundamentals of digital marketing from Google - Jan 2023

Web design course using WordPress from Vision

Academy - Mar 2022

Projects

- Developed Self static website using html, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap.
- Social Media Marketing for GetFem.

Work Experience

GETFEM

SOCIAL MEDIA EXECUTIVE

July 2020 – June 2021

Social Media Account Handling.

UNICARE PHARMA HUB PHARMACIST

September 2021 - Aug 2023

Dispensing Medicines and Prescription Handling.

PRECISION TECHNOLOGIES VALIDATION ENGINEER

July 2023 – Present

 Designing validation protocols, Testing and documentation, Compliance....etc.

Languages

- > English
- Hindi
- Marathi